<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>crypto on Black Bauhinia</title>
    <link>https://b6a.black/tags/crypto/</link>
    <description>Recent content in crypto on Black Bauhinia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:39:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://b6a.black/tags/crypto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>TetCTF 2021: unevaluated</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2021-01-03-tetctf-unevaluated/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:39:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2021-01-03-tetctf-unevaluated/</guid>
      <description>TetCTF is the first CTF I have played in 2021. I recalled from last year that they have cool challenges. This year, there are three crypto challenges. In particular, unevaluated is the hardest among them. Although I did not solve them, I dug into rabbit holes and had a lot of struggle, uh, fun.
Challenge Summary There is a 128-bit prime $p$. Define $\cdot: \mathbb{Z}_{p^2}^2\times\mathbb{Z}_{p^2}^2\rightarrow\mathbb{Z}_{p^2}^2$ by
\[(x_1, y_1)\cdot(x_2, y_2) := \left(\left(x_1x_2-y_1y_2\right)\ \text{mod}\ p^2, \left(x_1y_2+y_1x_2\right)\ \text{mod}\ p^2\right),\]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hxp CTF 2020: Hyper</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-12-20-hxpctf-hyper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 23:53:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-12-20-hxpctf-hyper/</guid>
      <description>I was teamed up to play hxp CTF as @blackb6a last week. The hxp team had come up with a collection of hard challenges. In particular, there are two series of crypto challenges with a total of five parts. I will be writing on the hyper challenge and some follow-up and unanswered questions regarding to hyperelliptic curves.
â“˜ ğ—¢ğ—³ğ—³ğ—¶ğ—°ğ—¶ğ—®ğ—¹ ğ˜€ğ—¼ğ˜‚ğ—¿ğ—°ğ—²ğ˜€ ğ˜€ğ˜ğ—®ğ˜ğ—²ğ—± ğ˜ğ—µğ—®ğ˜ ğ˜ğ—µğ—¶ğ˜€ ğ—¶ğ˜€ ğ—ºğ—¶ğ˜€ğ—¹ğ—²ğ—®ğ—±ğ—¶ğ—»ğ—´
Seriously. I knew nothing on hyperelliptic curves prior to the CTF.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dragon CTF 2020 Writeup</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-11-23-dragonctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 04:33:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-11-23-dragonctf/</guid>
      <description>Dragon CTF 2020 is definitely had my best CTF moments. There are big brain moments and I have been mind-blown for multiple times during the game. This time we have teamed up with @blackb6a. I have solved all the crypto challenges and two challenges with my teammates.
There are three challenges writeup in this post:
 Bit Flip (parts 2 and 3) Frying in motion babykok  Bit Flip (Crypto, 155+324+343 points) Solved by Mystiz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google CTF 2020: Oracle</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-08-25-google-ctf-oracle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 16:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-08-25-google-ctf-oracle/</guid>
      <description>I was teamed-up with @blackb6a on Google CTF this time. I have solved 7 challenges alone and 3 challenges with my teammates.
In particular, Oracle is a crypto challenge with 13 solves. It has got me spending 12 hours. All in all, it was a great experience in terms of learning, but my liver hurts. This piece of writeup may be very computation intensive, just because I would like to make everything clear.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>