<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Black Bauhinia</title>
    <link>https://b6a.black/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Black Bauhinia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 20:50:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://b6a.black/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hack.lu CTF 2021 Web Writeup</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2021-11-04-hacklu-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 20:50:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2021-11-04-hacklu-web/</guid>
      <description>Because there are not many Crypto listed in the &amp;quot;Stock Market&amp;quot;, our &lt;del&gt;Cryptotrader&lt;/del&gt; Cryptanalyst &lt;em&gt;Mystiz&lt;/em&gt; joined us for bounty hunting in Web as well, and we got all Web challenges done this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack.lu CTF 2021 Crypto Writeup</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2021-11-04-hacklu-crypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 20:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2021-11-04-hacklu-crypto/</guid>
      <description>Because there are not many Crypto listed in the &amp;quot;Stock Market&amp;quot;, I decided to join our &lt;del&gt;Webb-expert&lt;/del&gt; Web-expert &lt;em&gt;Ozetta&lt;/em&gt; for bounty hunting in web, and we got all web challenges done this time. The writeup of the web challenges can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DEFCON Gold Bug Puzzle 2021</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2021-08-19-defcon-gold-bug/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:25:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2021-08-19-defcon-gold-bug/</guid>
      <description>We played the annual Gold Bug puzzle hosted by the DEFCON Crypto and Privacy Village - and we won! Although we were unable to ace the challenge before the game ends, we managed to solve the remaining challenge afterwards. We will be covering all of them in this walkthrough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3kCTF-2021 Writeup</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2021-05-22-3kctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2021-05-22-3kctf/</guid>
      <description>We are united to play 3kCTF-2021 and result in the second place. In this blog post, we will walk through our solutions on the challenges solved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Apocalypse 2021: Wii Phit &amp; Hyper Metroid</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2021-04-25-htbctf-crypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 23:53:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2021-04-25-htbctf-crypto/</guid>
      <description>We played Cyber Apocalypse 2021 and I have attempted several crypto challenges. I&#39;ll include the challenges Wii Phit and Hyper Metroid in this writeup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DiceCTF 2021: Lost in your Eyes</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2021-02-09-dicectf-liye/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 02:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2021-02-09-dicectf-liye/</guid>
      <description>Lost in Your Eyes is a reverse engineering challenge in DiceCTF 2021 with ten solves (334 points). We are given a binary which takes an input and outputs either :) or :(. If you win a smiley face on the remote server, you are additionally given the flag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TetCTF 2021: unevaluated</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2021-01-03-tetctf-unevaluated/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:39:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2021-01-03-tetctf-unevaluated/</guid>
      <description>TetCTF is the first CTF I have played in 2021. I recalled from last year that they have cool challenges. This year, there are three crypto challenges. In particular, unevaluated is the hardest among them. Although I did not solve them, I dug into rabbit holes and had a lot of struggle, uh, fun.
Challenge Summary There is a 128-bit prime $p$. Define $\cdot: \mathbb{Z}_{p^2}^2\times\mathbb{Z}_{p^2}^2\rightarrow\mathbb{Z}_{p^2}^2$ by
\[(x_1, y_1)\cdot(x_2, y_2) := \left(\left(x_1x_2-y_1y_2\right)\ \text{mod}\ p^2, \left(x_1y_2+y_1x_2\right)\ \text{mod}\ p^2\right),\]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hxp CTF 2020: Hyper</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-12-20-hxpctf-hyper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 23:53:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-12-20-hxpctf-hyper/</guid>
      <description>I was teamed up to play hxp CTF as @blackb6a last week. The hxp team had come up with a collection of hard challenges. In particular, there are two series of crypto challenges with a total of five parts. I will be writing on the hyper challenge and some follow-up and unanswered questions regarding to hyperelliptic curves.
â“˜ ğ—¢ğ—³ğ—³ğ—¶ğ—°ğ—¶ğ—®ğ—¹ ğ˜€ğ—¼ğ˜‚ğ—¿ğ—°ğ—²ğ˜€ ğ˜€ğ˜ğ—®ğ˜ğ—²ğ—± ğ˜ğ—µğ—®ğ˜ ğ˜ğ—µğ—¶ğ˜€ ğ—¶ğ˜€ ğ—ºğ—¶ğ˜€ğ—¹ğ—²ğ—®ğ—±ğ—¶ğ—»ğ—´
Seriously. I knew nothing on hyperelliptic curves prior to the CTF.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dragon CTF 2020 Writeup</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-11-23-dragonctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 04:33:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-11-23-dragonctf/</guid>
      <description>Dragon CTF 2020 is definitely had my best CTF moments. There are big brain moments and I have been mind-blown for multiple times during the game. This time we have teamed up with @blackb6a. I have solved all the crypto challenges and two challenges with my teammates.
There are three challenges writeup in this post:
 Bit Flip (parts 2 and 3) Frying in motion babykok  Bit Flip (Crypto, 155+324+343 points) Solved by Mystiz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TokyoWesterns CTF 6th 2020 Writeup</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-09-23-twctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 00:53:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-09-23-twctf/</guid>
      <description>urlcheck v1 (Web, 98 points) Solved by Ozetta.
Objective: SSRF http://127.0.0.1/admin-status The input needs to fulfil the pattern &#39;\A(\d+)\.(\d+)\.(\d+)\.(\d+)\Z&#39; and the first octet cannot be 0 or 127, and some other patterns for internal IP addresses. For some reason, int(&amp;quot;0177&amp;quot;) is still 177 instead of 127 in Python, so we can use http://0177.0.0.1/admin-status
urlcheck v2 (Web, 128 points) Solved by Ozetta.
Objective: SSRF http://localhost/admin-status Standard TOCTOU bug, just use DNS rebinding to get access: http://23bbd91c.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CONFidence 2020 CTF: Team Trees</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-09-08-confidencectf-team-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 18:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-09-08-confidencectf-team-trees/</guid>
      <description>This week, we have teamed up as @blackb6a to play CONFidence 2020 CTF. We end up ranked 15, but we are more proud of ourselves able to solve a reversing challenge called Team Trees (395 points, 5 solves).
In particular, we are the first-to-solve to the challenge. It took us around two hours to win the flag. This writeup is written by @harrier_lcc and @mystiz613.
Challenge Summary  We wanted to plant a lot of trees, but it&#39;s going kinda slow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google CTF 2020: Oracle</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-08-25-google-ctf-oracle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 16:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-08-25-google-ctf-oracle/</guid>
      <description>I was teamed-up with @blackb6a on Google CTF this time. I have solved 7 challenges alone and 3 challenges with my teammates.
In particular, Oracle is a crypto challenge with 13 solves. It has got me spending 12 hours. All in all, it was a great experience in terms of learning, but my liver hurts. This piece of writeup may be very computation intensive, just because I would like to make everything clear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3kCTF-2020 Writeup</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-07-28-3kctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 11:36:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-07-28-3kctf/</guid>
      <description>reporter (Web; 498 points) Solved by apple.
Author: rekter0
 Reporter is an online markdown reporting tool. it&#39;s free to use for everyone. there&#39;s a secret report we need located here
source
 Walkthrough The application provide markdown hosting service and it will automatically download and embed external images (or any files) to the &#39;report&#39;.
There are 4 buttons on the interface: Edit, Preview, Save, and Deliver.
The first target of the challenge is to access the secret_report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UIUCTF 2020: Bot Protection IV</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-07-22-uiuctf-bot-protection-iv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 18:55:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-07-22-uiuctf-bot-protection-iv/</guid>
      <description>In this challenge, we have a website with captcha. Base on the question, we need to solve 500 captcha within 10 minutes. Very easy right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UIUCTF 2020: deserializeme</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-07-22-uiuctf-deserializeme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 18:55:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-07-22-uiuctf-deserializeme/</guid>
      <description>Update: It was assigned as CVE-2020-14343 after the contest.
 This was a fun challenge exploiting a deserialize service in Python.
The server is using pyYAML and Flask, with the source code below:
from flask import Flask, session, request, make_response import yaml import re import os app = Flask(__name__) app.secret_key = os.urandom(16) @app.route(&amp;#39;/&amp;#39;, methods=[&amp;#34;POST&amp;#34;]) def pwnme(): if not re.fullmatch(b&amp;#34;^[\n --/-\]a-}]*$&amp;#34;, request.data, flags=re.MULTILINE): return &amp;#34;Nice try!&amp;#34;, 400 return yaml.load(request.data) if __name__ == &amp;#39;__main__&amp;#39;: app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UIUCTF 2020: nookcrypt</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-07-22-uiuctf-nookcrypt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 18:55:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-07-22-uiuctf-nookcrypt/</guid>
      <description>Challenge Summary  Tom Nook is testing a new encryption scheme for nookphones, but it seems to be a bit faulty... can you break it?
 nookcrypt is a netcat service that have no source code released. There are two functions exposed:
 Gets an encrypted copy of the flag (and the message hello world). Encrypts an arbitrary message.  For example, this is what I had when trying out the options:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CONFidence 2020 Teaser CTF: Chromatic Aberration</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-07-01-confidencectf-teaser-chromatic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 15:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2020-07-01-confidencectf-teaser-chromatic/</guid>
      <description>In this CTF Question, author introduced a OOB read and arbitary write to the Array.fill of the V8 engine. So, our exploitation will be very straightforward. First, we will set up an array of BitInts with 0x33313131 as marking for arbitary write after we collect sufficient primitive with the OOB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PwnThyBytes CTF 2019 Writeup</title>
      <link>https://b6a.black/posts/2019-10-02-pwnthybytes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 23:20:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b6a.black/posts/2019-10-02-pwnthybytes/</guid>
      <description>Pass the Hash (Warmup/Learning; 50 points) Solved by Mystiz.
Challenge Summary We are given a peculiar hash algorithm that generates 64-byte long hashes, which wraps of sha0, sha1, sha256 and ripemd160. The hash takes two arguments, salt (20 bytes) and password (22 bytes). We are allowed to control the salt, whilst the goal is to find the password within 1024 queries.
Hash construction We are given a peculiar hash algorithm that generates 64-byte long hashes, which wraps of sha0, sha1, sha256 and ripemd160.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
